https://goalpost.tv/privacy-policy

your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Soccer & Football Blog
Home
World
AllSouth AmericaArgentinaWorld Cup 2010World Cup 2010 QualifyingWorld Cup 2014
Privacy Policy
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.
(1)    What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:
(a)    information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views);
(b)    information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us ;
(c)    information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters;
(de)    any other information that you choose to send to us;
(2)    Cookies
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website.  We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit;
Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser.  Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website.  Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers.  The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information.  Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.goalpost.tv.
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.goalpost.tv and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.
Our advertising partners include ….
Google Adsense
Commission Junction
Amazon
Betfair
Paddy Power
Expekt
Ladbrokes
Creafi
Skybet
Our advertisers may also send you cookies.
We publish Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on our website.  These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests.  To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies.  You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google’s Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/.  You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.  However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin.
Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies.  For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.  Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.
(3)    Using your personal data
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
(a)    administer the website;
(b)    improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;
(c)    enable your use of the services available on the website;
(d)    send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
(e)    send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
(f)    send to you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications)
(g)    deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;
Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.
We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, Paypal.  You should only provide your personal information to Paypal after reviewing the Paypal privacy policy (available at www.paypal.com).  We will share information with  Paypal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.
(4)     Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.
In addition, we may disclose information about you:
(a)    to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b)    in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c)    in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);
(d)    to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.;
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
(5)    Security of your personal data
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.
Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.
(6)    Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.
(7)    Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you.  Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).
You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email  at any time.  (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)
(8)    Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
(9)    Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
(10)     Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please contact us by email at info[..at..]goalpost.tv or phone +44(0)20 8123 3144
Stay connected
London
overcast clouds
enter location
9.3
°
C
10
December 11, 2020 0
17:30 Bochum v Paderborn at Ruhrstadion17:30 Sandhausen v SPVGG Greuther Fürth at Hardtwaldstadion
Superliga Fixtures for Friday 11th December 2020
Football Blog -
December 11, 2020 0
18:00 Randers FC v Vejle Boldklub at AutoC Park Randers
EDITOR PICKS
POPULAR POSTS
Western United FC
v Brisbane Roar FC
Football Team...
February 16, 2020
Bordeaux
v Dijon
Football Team Lineup – Ligue 1...
February 15, 2020
Karpaty
v SC Dnipro-1
Football Team Lineup – Ukrainian...
November 30, 2019
POPULAR CATEGORYBetting Odds96813Football Results29160Videos17640Upcoming Matches14283Tommorrows Matches668Olympics 2012 Football370Premier League160National Teams155Euro 2012 Quick News141
ABOUT USgoalpost.tv is your football blog !Contact us: info@goalpost.tv
© goalpost.tv | cold sores ireland
|
wigs in los angeles
